DEVDEEP BANERJEE

devdeep14.github.io/devportfolio

Game Developer

+91 9916267332



devdeep01@gmail.com



/devdeep-banerjee



github.com/devdeep14



PROFILE

Passionate game maker, completed Master's degree in Game Technology from ICAT Design & Media college. Having 4+ years of corporate experience as a digital designer in website design and development. Seeking an opportunity to enter the gaming industry having proficient knowledge in Game Development tools such as Unity and Unreal game engines with understanding of materials/shaders. Also, worked in 3D modeling tools like Maya and ProBuilder.

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN
GAME TECHNOLOGY (MSc)

ICAT Design & Media College 2021 - 2023

BACHELORS IN COMPUTER APPLICATION (BCA)

Bangalore University 2013 - 2016

Completing my masters in game technology from ICAT design & media college, affiliated to Alagappa University

Learnt the basics of game design challenges & development process along with game engines such as Unity & Unreal with understanding of materials/shaders.

For final year project, working on an action-adventure FPS shooter game with sabotage missions on the backdrop of Kashmir, India.

Completed my graduation in computer science from City College - Jayanagar, affiliated to Bangalore University

For final year project, created fully-functional insurance website which consists of purchase, claim & renew policy sections to manage user's account details

WORK EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL DESIGNER

Element14 Sept, 2019 - Sept, 2021 Part of Global Creative Services team, designing & developing complete marketing campaigns for element14 Asia-Pacific and clients based in Farnell EU & Newark NA

Creating form integrated landing pages & designing homepage leaderboard, supplier funded banners / product slots and merchandising eSpot banners

Brand reviewed marketing campaigns deployed across 42 sites in 26 languages, also worked in Adobe Target A/B testing for analyzing campaign results

WEB & GRAPHICS DESIGNER

CRMIT Solutions July, 2017 - July, 2019 Designing, developing & maintaining company website along with creating marketing emailer campaigns and product landing pages.

Creating visual imagery for company branding, creating corporate brochures, whitepapers, infographics and marketing slides

COURSES

• UNREAL ENGINE 5 C++ DEVELOPER

GameDev.tv Team - Udemy 2022 - 2023

• COMPLETE C# UNITY GAME DEVELOPER 2D & 3D

GameDev.tv Team - Udemy 2022 - 2023

SKILLS

- C / C++ / C#
- Unity Game Engine
- Unreal Game Engine
- HTML-CSS / Bootstrap
- Photoshop / Illustrator
- Adobe XD / Figma
- Maya
- Substance 3D

KEY INTERESTS

- Game Concept & Ideation
- Game Design & Visualization
- Visual Motion Graphics

SOFT SKILLS

- Critical-thinking
- Strong analytical
- Problem solving abilities

HOBBIES











